(Leonard:)He's got what we need
and can meet us tonight.
Oh, really?
You know I don't like
buying things at night.
January 7, 2009.
I went to the Ralph's
at 11:30pm to pick up
Cracklin' Oat Bran for the
morning and what did I see?
(Leonard:)The man restocking
the cereal shelves.
(Sheldon:)That's right.
And what did he do?
(Leonard:)He handed you the box directly
and called you Stretch.
(shudders)
(Sheldon:)It's like it was yesterday.
(Leonard:)Do you want
liquid helium or not?
(Sheldon:)Of course I do.
(Sheldon:)I don't want that
Swedish team scooping us.
(Leonard:)Then I'm going
to tell him we're in.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, wait.
This is highly unethical.
(Leonard:)We're just bending
the rules a little.
(Leonard:)We have grant money
to do the experiment,
(Leonard:)so we're going to spend it
on the helium we need.
(Leonard:)It's not like when Dr. Goldfarb
(Leonard:)claimed he bought
an electron microscope
(Leonard:)and he was really just keeping
(Leonard:)a Russian girl
in an apartment in Van Nuys.
(Sheldon:)Was she helping him
with his research?
(Stuart:)Sure.